All right. So, for a lot of our fans
that haven't had the opportunity to
watch Jaylen Phillips and you're
wondering why this guy is getting paid
so much money, we're going to jump right
into this now and we're going to show
you exactly why cuz he brings so many
different elements to the game. He has
speed, he has power, he has finishing
moves, he has the ability to go out and
completely wreck a game. over 70 plus
pressures on the quarterback really
speaks to what he brings to the table.
So, we're gonna jump right into this
film. Dan, let's do it.
>> And he can rush outside, he can rush
inside, you know, he has all those
things. Here's a here's an example of
him on a guard on the inside, utilizing
his length and power to disrupt the the
passer. So,
>> and ironically enough, against the
Falcons, what
>> Yeah, exactly. adding this type of frame
that is so versatile that he can be he
can play outside linebacker, you can put
him inside on third down, you can do
different things with him. He's just
going to bring a ton to our defense.
>> Yes. Love it. Now you see him out here
on the edge
again showing that versatility.
>> Yeah. And he's still young, you know.
He's still a guy that's young and and he
is still developing in terms of pass
rush arsenal. So, I think, you know, we
haven't seen the best Jaylen Phillips,
which is kind of scary. Yeah.
>> Because he's already a really good
player.
>> Love to see it.
>> This is arguably one of the best tackles
in the league that he's going against
for those of you guys out there
watching. And look how easily he beat
him on this.
>> Yeah. Hand timing off the edge. You
know, things you can't teach, right?
Like, you can work on it, but you got
actually got to go out there against,
like you said, one of the best right
tackles in the league and do play. Yeah.
And you saw you saw a bull rush. You saw
him working his hands. And then right
here, you see the speed, you see the
hand movement, all of the things that we
just talked about, you get to pull up
the film and watch it in real life. And
Jaylen Phillips has all of those tools
in his bag.
>> Yeah. and he just I mean the relentless
motor to the ball and like you see here
just making plays up and down the line
of scrimmage showing off his athleticism
and you know he just has he has a lot
and he brings a lot to the table for us.
>> What did you see out of Jaylen on this
play?
>> To me this is film study and it's also
just kind of knowing your opponents and
you know you could tell right here like
he knew he knew what was coming. Um so
his ability
>> get off too.
>> Yeah. just like anticipating the snap,
getting off the ball, knifing off the
backside, flattening out down the line
of scrimmage and finishing.
>> Yep.
>> You know, it's another impact play to
where you put a team at a disadvantage,
one two yard loss and then all of a
sudden you're behind the sticks.
>> I don't think too many teams are going
to try to block him with a tight end
from outside.
>> Yeah, he probably shouldn't.
>> Not Not a good idea.
>> And we're going to ask him to do a lot
of this. So, like you see him get off
the ball,
>> patton hands.
>> Yep. you know, setting the setting the
edge. We're big about setting the edge
here. Setting the edge and not only
setting the edge, but time t timeing up,
getting off the block and making the
play.
>> And you talked about this not trading
one for one. Yeah,
>> that's something that you never want to
see a guy do.
>> I feel like Jaylen Phillips does this
consistently, being able to get off the
block and finish on plays. Is that one
of the things that you've saw out of him
as a strength?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I think his his run
defense, I think, is very underrated.
You know, to be that big of a guy, like
you would expect him to set the edge and
make these type of plays, and he does.
So, he's going to bring a lot to our
defense, not just from a pass rushing
standpoint, but on first and second down
verse teams that are trying to pound the
ball, he's going to be able to make an
impact versus the run as well.
>> In your decision to assign him, did you
make any any phone calls down
to Miami, Florida. Ask any of your guys
about him?
>> Absolutely.
>> What is some of the information they
told you about him when he from when he
was a college kid?
>> They same same stuff you see on tape. It
matched up with what everybody told me.
is this guy not just on game day but
during the week he's full throttle like
he him and Nick Scorton sound almost
exactly alike in terms of guys that just
like it doesn't matter if it's a
Wednesday practice Thursday Friday
>> they they love ball and they they just
play so hard talk about his speaking of
playing hard talk about his ability to
fight through this hold on this play
right here
>> yeah I mean
>> he could have easily threw his hands up
to the ref and like He held me, which we
see guys do a lot of time,
>> but he he understood I got to get to the
quarterback still, even after being
held.
>> I got to make sure that I make this play
just in case they don't call it.
>> Yeah. I mean, look at for being as big
as he is and to have the body quickness
and the twitch first of all to cross his
face right here
>> and to be able to bend and finish
>> and then stay on his feet and redirect
down the line of scrimmage. Like again,
like he's an athlete, you know? You
can't teach that.
>> This is another thing that I love right
here because you see the discipline
because yeah,
>> a lot of players in this, you know, the
quarterback is reading the end man on
the line of scrimmage. So,
>> he's reading the he's reading them. So,
he's slow played it and still was able
to do his job taking the quarterback
away and get down the line. So, that
just shows me the one that he's a
disciplined player. Two, he has the
speed and athleticism to be able to
recover and make a play like that. So, I
mean,
>> yeah, he can just he can do a lot.
>> Hey, man, made a great decision.
>> Yeah. I mean, again, like
>> him being able to do a lot of stuff, you
know,
>> and we know how athletic Mr. Love is and
he
>> and if you look at our schedule too, we
play against a lot of athletic
quarterbacks this year.
>> So, we get you got to have athletes out
on the field and this is just another
athlete
Hey,